homesthetics.net 2014-06-02

# Privacy Policy | Homesthetics - Inspiring ideas for your home.

[

### __Privacy Policy

](http://www.homesthetics.net/privacy-policy/)

**0** Flares **0** Flares ×

**Privacy Policy of Homesthetics**

[Homesthetics](http://homesthetics.com/) , will always respect your privacy and will always be committed to protect the personal information you may provide us through our website.

The Privacy Policy is meant to explain what information may be collected by [Homesthetics](http://homesthetics.com/), how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties if needed.  
**  
The Information We Gather and How We Use It**

Our Website typically collects two types of information about you depending on your actions:

Information that you provide that personally identifies you as a individual  
If you send us an e-mail or a comment, you may choose to provide us with personal information, such as your name or your e-mail address. We try to use the information provided to get better, to respond to your needs as soon as possible and offer you a better service and information overall.

We will never ask your personal information and if you are choosing to provide us that information it is mainly because it is required in an action you would like to benefit from, you can always choose to just read the article, however in many instances this type of information is required to gain access to certain content or to be a part of a conversation .

Information that does not personally identify you, that we automatically collect when you visit our Website

If you are just browsing trough our website, read pages or download information for example, we will gather certain specific information about your visit, by default, automatically. This information does not identify you as an individual . Most of the time we gather and store details about your visit such as the Internet Domain (for example, “website.com” if you use a private Internet Access Account), your IP (Internet Protocol) address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are browsing the internet) or other small details like type of browser and operating system that is used to gain access to our content, the pages you visit, the date and time you access the website or if you linked our website from another website and the specific address to which you have linked our site.

We use the gathered information to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you and more fit to you needs, for example if you like the articles related to self sustainability more then the others we will try and disclose that field further on as much as we can.

**Your Information is Secure**

We have implemented security measures that we consider reasonable and appropriate to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control and we are always trying our best to improve those methods. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. From time to time we evaluate new technology for protecting information, and when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems.

**Cookies**

To save you comment’s information every time you visit our website [Homesthetics](http://homesthetics.com/), we place a little text file called a “cookie” on your hard drive. It sits in your web browser directory.

A cookie allows us to store your profile information on your computer and lets our website retrieve it when you visit our site. No other website can use or view the cookie set by [Homesthetics](http://homesthetics.com/).

Cookies are meant to help us create a faster web experience by remembering your address and email information, so you don’t have to re-type it you want to take part in a conversation or leave your opinion by using the comment section.

We may use cookies on the website for the purpose of monitoring your and other users’ activity in order to improve the website and the services available to you. If you don’t want us to use cookies when you use our website, you will need to change your Internet browser settings so that your browser does not accept them.

**Links to Other Sites**

[Homesthetics](http://homesthetics.net/) has some specific links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new website.

**Restriction of Liability**

[Homesthetics](http://homesthetics.net/) makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may change some of the statements in this Privacy Policy at any time. We will prominently post notice of the changes at this URL. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective when posted.

Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof and if it`s the case and if we make any changes to this privacy policy stated above, we will post them on our website in order to keep you in touch, in this way you will always know what personal data we collect, how we use it, and what your legal rights are.

If you have any other concerns or questions please  **contact  us**.

**0** Flares Twitter 0 Facebook 0 Google+ 0 StumbleUpon 0 Email \-- **0** Flares ×
